<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on TrueKYC</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on TrueKYC</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Processing Agreement (DPA)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dpa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dpa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Personal Data Processing Agreement (hereinafter “Agreement“) is supplemental to the Terms and Conditions (also “Master Agreement”) and applies as set out therein.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Agreement sets out the additional terms, requirements, and conditions under which the Service Provider (hereinafter TRUEZONE Inc.) will process Personal Information when providing Services under the Terms and Conditions. This Agreement contains mandatory clauses required under applicable Data Protection Laws for contracts regarding data sharing and data processing activities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how TRUEZONE Inc. (&amp;ldquo;TRUEZONE,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;) collects, uses, discloses, and protects personal information in connection with the platform. This Policy is applicable to Customers who collect personal information from their Applicants through TRUEZONE’s services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Scope and Applicability&#xA;This Policy applies to personal information collected by our Customers from their Applicants, which includes individuals whose information is processed in connection with the use of TRUEZONE&amp;rsquo;s platform. This Policy is applicable to all Customers, regardless of their geographical location, including but not limited to those in the EU, California, and other states in the United States. This ensures a comprehensive understanding of data processing practices for all users.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition, this Policy considers applicable regulations in various jurisdictions, including but not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terms &amp; Conditions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/terms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Personal Data Processing Agreement (hereinafter “Agreement“) is supplemental to the Terms and Conditions (also “Master Agreement”) and applies as set out therein.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Agreement sets out the additional terms, requirements, and conditions under which the Service Provider (hereinafter TRUEZONE Inc.) will process Personal Information when providing Services under the Terms and Conditions. This Agreement contains mandatory clauses required under applicable Data Protection Laws for contracts regarding data sharing and data processing activities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
